(Leonard:)Leslie Winkle.
(Leslie:)Yeah, Leslie Winkle.
The answer to the question:
"Who made Sheldon Cooper cry
like a little girl?"
Yes, well, I'm polymerized tree sap,
and you're an inorganic adhesive.
(Sheldon:)So whatever verbal projectile you launch
in my direction is reflected off of me...
(Sheldon:)...returns on its original trajectory,
and adheres to you.
(Leslie:)Oh, ouch.
(Dr Gablehouser:)Okay, if everyone could please
take your seats?
Here's your T-shirt.
(Leslie:)PMS?
It's a couple days early.
(Leonard:)No.
(Leonard:)It stands for Perpetual Motion Squad.
(Leslie:)Oh, right, of course.
What was I thinking?
(Gablehouser:)Good afternoon, everyone,
and welcome to this year's Physics Bowl.